Previously on
Pretty Little Liars...
For us making it to senior year.
Not all of us made it.
Can you see, or not?
No.
The surgery didn't--
No, it didn't.
Garrett Reynolds, you're under arrest.
For what?
The murder of
Alison Dilaurentis.
Is miss Rivers available?
How did you get my number?
Hey. Everything okay
I need a lawyer, and your mom's
one of the best in the state.
I'm not going to help you.
I think I remember
leaving your house,
and the next thing I know,
I'm here.
You guys, this is a set-up.
It's not "A."
Mona is drooling in her bed
at a nut hospital.
We don't know that for sure.
- I've been visiting her.
- What?!
"Mona played with dolls--
I play with body parts."
"Game on, bitches."
"A."
The author goes to great
lengths to establish Hedda Gabler
as a strong, proud woman,
someone who could never live with
the threat of being blackmailed.
But Hedda was pushed
to take a desperate action.
And while she may have
seen it as brave,
we see it as tragic.
What might really be tragic
is if some of you
don't start taking some notes.
Sorry. Senior year is not
all about skipping classes
and dancing for the security
cameras at Walmart.
That's what
your weekends are for.
You might also want to research
some of his other plays
and see how they were
received at that time...
Emily, is everything all right?
C-can I be excused?
Emily--
What's going on?
No, no. Just come on.
Em, what's the matter?
Talk to us.
What is that?
Are those teeth?
Please just get rid of it.
now we're gonna get
pieces of her delivered to us?
Guys, there probably aren't even human.
They're totally human!
How do you know? Because I
worked at a dentist's office.
For two days, answering phones. Yeah,
and there were teeth everywhere.
Even the friggin' bathroom key
was shaped like a cuspid.
Guys, real or not, this "A" is
working overtime to frame us.
First the call to Emily
from Spencer's phone,
then the cemetery photo, and now--
It's all my fault.
Em, stop. No. That whole
night is like a black hole.
I still can't figure out
how I got to Ali's grave.
We need to give this
to the police.
We can't. We already lied
to them about the lake house.
Yeah. That was
a huge mistake.
We keep digging ourselves
in deeper.
Burning those photos
was one thing--
These are teeth. Okay?
We should at least tell our parents.
Tell them what?
We have no idea
what this "A" knows.
Are you ready to explain every lie
we've ever told since Ali died?
You don't have to
protect me, okay?
I can take the blame
for all of this.
Emily, stop.
You're not in this by yourself.
But if you could
remember something else
from that black hole
besides an old car,
that'd be nice.
Hanna.
I'm just saying,
it'd be helpful.
Can we please
just get rid of that?
We can't toss this.
This is evidence.
I'll put it in my locker
until we figure out what to do.
Like your locker
is safe from "A"?
Just give it to me.
I'll put it in my purse--
Hanna.
I will get it.
No, wait!
You can't just dive in there.
These things have sensors.
Excuse me? You just have
to be really careful.
Well, if you would like to. No.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Got a secret,
can you keep it ♪
♪ swear this one you'll save
♪ better lock it
in your pocket ♪
♪ takin' this one
to the grave ♪
♪ if I show you, then I know
you won't tell what I said ♪
♪ 'cause two can keep a secret
if one of them is dead ♪
I can't believe we've lost it.
It wasn't like we were
gonna hand it over to the cops.
I wanted to. We could have
found out who sent it to us.
There were fingerprints on that necklace.
Yeah, mine.
Hanna, you have to go back to Radley.
What?
You need to make Mona talk.
Spencer's right.
Mona has never
been working alone,
and she's probably still
giving people orders.
Find out who else has seen her.
You guys just ripped me a new
one last week for visiting her.
Now you want me to
go back there with cupcakes?
If we want answers,
focusing on Garrett.
I will go back to Garrett,
if you will work on Mona.
Will you go today?
After school?
Has anyone spoken to her
since school started?
No. I still think
it's really shady
that she didn't get back from Music Camp
until the first day of school.
It's no shadier than Lucas
strolling around
on Saturday
at four in the morning.
Well, maybe that's
their witching house.
So now we think
they're definitely connected?
Jenna and Lucas?
Em, you saw them talking to that Black Swan person
at the masquerade party.
Mona could have an entire
outfield playing for her.
Hey, watch it.
Here you go, man. That's okay,
Jenna, don't worry about it.
Is it just me or is she blinder
than she was last year?
Hey. Still working on this?
Yeah, but I can fix it.
The school should be paying you.
A lot.
What's up?
You okay?
Um, I do have to
meet my mom after school.
She wants me to help
pick out an outfit
for this bank thingie,
so can we do dinner
tomorrow night instead?
Yeah.
Tomorrow night's fine.
Great. Well,
see you later, sweetie.
Your mom thinks
I'm a basket case.
My mom loves you, em.
She knows everything
that you've been through.
Can she spread the love
around the faculty lounge?
I have to take
four make-up exams
or they're gonna make me
repeat eleventh grade.
They can't hold you back.
Yes, they can.
I was absent all of April.
You're gonna get through this.
Maybe.
You just need
a study partner. A tutor.
Wait!
Why don't you just call Ezra?
If your first make-up test is an
English he could be your tutor.
awkward.
No, it's not.
Aria, I can't think of him
as "Mr. Fitz" anymore.
Okay? I've seen
his underwear drawer.
Those were his socks. Why would his
socks have a flap in the middle?
I'm texting you his number.
Aria, I don't--
He's not teaching right now,
and it's killing him.
You'd be helping
each other out.
Who is that?
Meredith.
Wait. That's
your dad's Meredith?
That's the skank you and Ali
caught lip-locking in the car?
If my mom sees her here...
What's she doing here?
Excuse me.
Are you looking for someone?
Hello, Aria. I forgot
you were still a student here.
Yeah, I am.
What are you doing here?
I'm applying for
an open teaching position.
Oh, don't worry, hon. I won't
put you down as a reference.
I don't get it.
Why would she want
to work at a school
where she's gonna bump into
my mother every single day?
And why should my mom
have to go through this?
She's been divorced
for, like, 20 minutes.
Aria, breathe. Meredith
applied for the job,
it doesn't mean she got it.
There's no reason
to tell your mom.
Seriously, though, who is giving
that woman a reference--my dad?
Ooh, yeah, I wouldn't
tell him either.
Why? You think he has
something to do with this?
I didn't say that,
I just think you're still
walking on bit of scorched
earth when it comes to us,
and if you put him on the defensive--
He's not in that place anymore.
Then why am I dropping you off
three blocks from your house?
Because he's still
in that place.
I hate this. I hate
having to sneak around
and avoid saying your name...
It's like
we're going backwards.
One battle at a time.
We just had a nice dinner--
with your mom.
Okay? Let's celebrate
what is working.
It's Emily. Has she
called you yet? No.
Why haven't you
called Ezra yet?
Call him now.
He's free.
Emily's gonna be calling you.
I might not answer.
Ezra, she's sinking.
Please?
So, um...
Did you talk to your mom?
No. I need you to give me
a better reason.
Other than being innocent?
Look, you said you knew
who dug up Ali's grave.
How do I know that the person
didn't just do that for you?
I didn't touch your friend Maya,
and I didn't kill Alison,
and guess what, what was snatched
from her grave that night
would have actually proved it.
How?
Is your mom
defending me or not?
Why would she or anyone else in this
town believe that you're innocent?
Spencer, somebody you know well
has you completely fooled.
People lie, but...
Medical records don't.
Whose medical records?
Who are you talking about?
Alison?
Jenna's?
Wait.
Are you talking about Jenna?
So it turns out ***
that frizzy-haired girl
who dates the quarterback.
You know, the one
who transferred from Ohio?
Well, Noel Kahn thinks
this dude is a genius
because he can burp
the star-spangled banner.
Have you...
Heard from Noel?
Does he ever come visit you?
Has anyone... Been to
visit you besides me?
You know what, Mona?
If I told the police
that you mowed me down
with your car,
you would not be here getting a slice of
peach pie every day to wash down your meds.
You'd be sharing a jail cell with
someone calling you "Peach Pie"
while you braid her back hair!
God, Mona, you owe me!
All right? You have made my
life a nightmare! You owe me!
What's going on?
This visit's over.
Now.
Hey there.
Hi.
Can I get you a cup of coffee?
No, I'm okay.
Thanks, Mr. Fitz.
You can call me Ezra.
No, I can't.
But I can try.
Have a seat.
So...Aria mentioned
you're taking the English
make-up exam this Thursday.
Yeah, and then chem and history
next week, and Spanish after that.
Great. Well, I'm glad we can start
with a language I actually speak...in.
But not always so well.
Did you like the novel?
Yeah, it was okay.
Ending was kind of sad.
Emily, um...
I'm so sorry about Maya.
We don't have to
talk about that.
No. I know.
But it's just, I--
I wanted you to know that.
I'm just...Sorry.
Your friend Mona deserves
to be drawn and quartered.
And given what she's done, I
understand you want to punish her.
That's not why I came here.
I just lost it.
I've done worse.
I once threw a bowl of soup
across the room
when visiting my dad.
In a place much like this.
Worse.
Your dad was in the nut house?
For years.
He checked out of my life
when I was ten,
traded our family room
for the chaos inside his head.
He made your friend down the
hall seem downright chatty.
She won't even apologize.
Then you have to
accept that, Hanna.
You've lost someone
whom you trusted.
And then you might be grieving for the Mona you
didn't know as much as for the one you did.
I'm getting really tired
of losing people.
And this is particularly hard because
Mona's right in front of you.
In clinical terms,
we call it "ambiguous loss."
What? There's been a death, but
it doesn't involve a body.
Like when a soldier
goes missing,
or a relative
slips into dementia.
They're gone,
but yet, still here.
Here.
Where did Jenna go
when music camp ended?
Did your parents pick her up?
I have no idea. Why?
Well, that camp ended
on August 23rd.
I looked it up online.
Did she just stay up
in the Poconos?
Honestly, I don't know.
I was packing up my stuff
before she even went to camp.
Just eating breakfast there was weird.
How come?
My parents were treating Jenna
like one of her snow-globes.
After the surgery didn't work,
it was like they thought she'd crack
if they asked the wrong question.
Hey.
Hmm?
Come here.
You're a little tense.
Yeah.
I was born that way.
Maybe I can help.
♪ ...just a lie
♪ but I found you out
♪ and said my last goodbye
♪ so what happened to you,
darling.... ♪
Spencer?
Yeah! In here!
Oh.
Hello, Toby.
Hey, Mrs. Hastings,
how's it goin'?
I've had better days.
Did your sister call? I've left
three messages for her.
Uh, no, is Melissa okay?
I don't think "okay" really applies
in her situation, does it?
Will you be joining us
for dinner, Toby?
Uh...Well, I was--
Sure.
It was weird,
but we got past it.
So you're calling him "Ezra,"
or "Mr. Fitz"?
Neither. It's a lot easier
not to call him anything.
Oh. That's what your
dad does, right, Aria?
Just about. This whole "don't ask,
don't tell" thing is not working.
I did that with my mom forever.
But she finally came around.
By the time
I brought Tamara over,
they were bonding
over arts and crafts.
I don't think my dad is gonna be
scrapbookin' with Ezra anytime soon.
What's that?
Is that yours?
What's going on?
Whose is that?
Do you want to save your
parents' marriage, or not?
I don't even know
what we're looking for.
If my dad said that Meredith's
history, I believe him.
Oh, grow up. They probably
do it on that couch. Daily.
Do you smell cheap perfume?
Ali, there are other students
that come in here, okay?
Yeah,
and how many of them
like to roll around
and sweat on his couch?
Is that someone coming?
Which student
does this belong to?
You found that in his couch?
Honey, I'm sure she's shed
a lot more than that.
Probably find her panties
in the mini-fridge.
Oh. So they have been
spending quality time together.
I hear break-up sex
is the best.
Why would he lie? He told
me that he ended it.
Maybe he did, sweetie.
But people make up.
They backslide.
Aria, if you really want
to get rid of this bitch,
you're gonna have to help daddy
figure out what she really is--
a vindictive,
homewrecking bunny-boiler.
Don't look now, but mere-death
is having a meltdown.
How come you never told us about that?
Why would I?
I felt like complete crap
by the time I got home,
and I made Alison promise
to never tell a soul.
So why is it in your locker? You've
been hiding it this whole time?
No. No. It's just that
you guys...
Don't you remember when Ali's mom
called us before her funeral
and she asked all of us if we
each wanted to put something....
A keepsake in her casket?
And that's what
you put in there?
So real teeth or not, that was
definitely stolen from Ali's grave.
So next, cite an example of
how the author uses symbolism.
Emily?
I'm sorry,
what was the question?
Wharton's use of symbolism?
The cat.
The broken dish.
Emily...
You know this material,
and you've been in
high-pressure situations before.
When you were swimming,
you thrived on them, right?
So how did you
prepare for a race?
What did you do minutes
before you jumped in that pool?
Um, I...
Listened to music.
Then that's what you'll do
before you take these exams.
Everything you need to know
is already in your head.
Aria? Is that you?
Jenna.
I thought I recognized
the ringtone.
I was going to
call you tonight.
Why?
I lost my accompanist
for next week's assembly,
and I thought of askingyou
to play with me.
Oh. Uh...
I'm a little rusty.
Oh, it's an easy piece.
Just a couple of rehearsals
and we'd be good to go.
So you want to come over
tomorrow?
Gee, uh--uh--
I'd really love to, Jenna,
but I'm helping my dad with
this project he's doing, and--
He's actually waving at me from across
the street, so I really gotta go.
She invited
you to that house?
- What'd you say?
- I said no freakin' way. To myself.
But to her I just said
that I was busy.
Did you ever find a note? Are we
sure that earring came from "A"?
I'd be a lot more sure
if you could squeeze
something out of Mona.
Please tell me that
you're going back there.
Are you? Uh, I don't know.
I'll call you back.
Hey. Took long enough.
They messed up. Gave our
order to someone else.
Didn't you get my text?
Uh, no. I was
on the phone with Aria.
I'm starving.
Me too.
You got somewhere else
you need to be?
No. No.
Of course not.
Ask whoever that is
to call you back, please.
I-- I won't
answer it.
Everything okay?
No. Clearly it's not if my daughter's
making secret trips to the county jail.
There's still a lot of things
that I don't understand.
Yeah, me too, like why would
you have anything to do with
a man who's accused of murdering
two teenage girls?
Mom, Emily is really hurting,
and I just wanted some answers.
Did this happen to Maya
because she knew too much?
Did the D.A.'s office send you
there to ask that question?
I didn't think so.
I'm guessing it'll be
answered at his trial.
Why are you talking to me like I'm a hostile witness?
Maya was my friend, too.
This is a dangerous man,
Spencer.
He wouldn't be locked up if there
weren't damaging evidence against him.
Don't you ever go there again.
So is rosewood safe now that one
dangerous man is locked up?
Because garret was already in
jail when Ali's grave was dug up.
If you're implying that he's got
helpful friends on the outside,
that's even more of
a reason not to see him.
People might think that's you.
Don't you ever go there again.
Am I clear?
I thought you were starved.
Guess I'm not.
Okay, where do you
need to be right now?
Hanna, we stopped lying to
each other a long time ago,
didn't we?
I was thinking of
visiting Mona at Radley.
Why now?
Just curious.
It's complicated.
No, it's more than complicated.
It is completely whacked.
Look, she was my best friend
in tenth grade. Yeah,
and she threw you a few
poisoned apples in the eleventh.
I don't expect you to understand, all right?
I know you hate her.
I feel sorry for her, okay? But not
enough to send her a get well card.
- Caleb-- - I don't care if she spends the
rest of her life in a paper gown
making ash trays and pooping
in a stall without a door
as long as she can't get
anywhere near you, or hurt you--
It hurt me to
see her like this, okay?
I'm having an ambiguous loss.
You're what?
That's what it's called. Someone
dies but they're still here.
Where did you pick that up?
I googled it, okay?
I'm not gonna have this fight.
Fine.
I'll go with you.
What?
To Radley.
I'll drive you there.
By the time we get there
visiting hours will be over.
Then we'll go tomorrow.
Why would you do that?
Because I love you.
And I don't want us
sneaking around each other.
Dad?
Can I talk to you?
Yeah. What's wrong?
Will you sit down? I--
I need to tell you something.
Um...
I know that your office was
trashed a couple years ago.
And I know that
I'm not supposed to know that
because you thought that
it was Meredith who did it.
But it wasn't her, it was me.
Why are you
telling me this now?
Did seeing Meredith yesterday
bring this on?
I guess. Maybe.
Do you have any idea how close
I came to calling the police?
I thought she wanted to hurt my family.
She already had.
So I did it.
I said a lot of harsh things
to her at the time.
And now you're telling me that I
accused her of something that...
You did.
We both owe her an apology.
And I'm not doing that for you.
♪ ...yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ jump in,
floating like a feather-- ♪
You ready?
Okay, guys, you have 45 minutes.
I'll give you a five-minute warning
before I collect the tests.
Good luck.
So...
This won't be long.
If you need me,
I'll be right here, okay?
Hey, Mona.
I'm back.
I didn't come here
to throw any more chairs.
I just...
Wanted to return the favor.
I brought the good stuff.
How did you
get your hands on these?
Nobody was home. I found them
in Jenna's bathroom.
So what are they?
They're eye drops?
The doctor prescribed
the first bottle to Jenna
last spring after the surgery.
So?
Thank you.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Check out the expiration date
on the other bottle.
If the surgery didn't work, why is she
still renewing that prescription?
Wait. What are you saying?
You think Jenna can see?
Emily?
Are you okay?
Five minutes, guys.
Okay, time is up.
Emily...
It's not a take-home test.
Oh, right.
Sorry.
Did you need more time?
No, I'm done.
Emily, wait.
Did you study for this?
Yeah, I did. But I--
I did the best I could.
I really have to go.
Hello.
Hi.
Do you want to sit?
I'd...really rather not
do this here, if that's okay.
Well, here is where we are.
Sit.
Look, I-- I know that
this is ancient history,
but I just needed
to clarify something.
After I found out about you and
my dad, I was really upset.
And I broke into his office--
You don't have to recount
all the gory details.
I spoke to your father
this morning.
I remember his threats on my
voicemail like it was yesterday.
Right.
Well, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Maybe I'll hear that from
your father tomorrow, too.
You're seeing him?
We made lunch plans.
And I guess I have you
to thank for that.
Is there something else
you want to say?
Yeah.
I didn't go to his office with the
intention of stealing anything,
I just took the earrings because--
Wait.
Go back. Earrings?
I don't have the other one, but as soon as
I find it I'll make sure that you get it.
What made you think
this belonged to me?
That's not my earring.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm just here
to visit Garrett Reynolds.
He's meeting with his lawyer.
It could be a while.
Oh. May I wait?
Suit yourself.
Thank you.
Can you give me a list of all
previous visitors, please?
Thanks.
No, no, no. I want something
compiled for the last five months.
I'll need a little
time to put that together.
Okay. Tomorrow?
Yeah, tomorrow works.
Okay, thanks.
Pardon me.
You're with Hanna?
I'm Dr. Kingston.
Hanna knows me as wren.
And you are?
Caleb.
Her boyfriend.
Very good. So you decided
to join her this time.
Yeah.
Yeah, Hanna pretty much does
whatever she wants,
so I figured
I would get onboard.
Indeed. Well,
from what I've gathered,
coming here has been a great
source of conflict for her.
She's spoken to you about this?
She has. We talked about
patience and compassion.
It seems like the other day was a
bit of a turning point for her.
She's just starting to
come to terms with
all the anger that's tied
to ambiguous loss.
Well, then, best press on.
But please give Hanna
my best. Nice meeting you.
Yeah. Same here.
What was my mother doing here?
Sorry. I can't talk.
My new attorney
made me promise.
What-- what are you saying?
Is my mother your lawyer now?
No. There's--
there's no way--
I never even asked her
to help you.
I couldn't, she still
thinks you're guilty.
What did you say that
made her change her mind?
I gotta go.
Wait.
- What about Jenna, though?
Could you at least tell me-- - I'm done.
Okay,
so the lighting in here sucks.
But at least you're starting to
look like someone I recognize.
Look, Mona,
I didn't come here
to play beauty shop.
I came here because I know there
is a person still in there.
I know you've been hurt,
but so have I.
And I still am.
Trust me, you're not the first
person to hurt me, Mona.
And you're certainly
not the last.
You're getting them
again, aren't you?
The texts.
Hey, Hanna. The nurse said
that visiting hours are over.
Um, yeah, can you, uh,
can you give me a minute?
Just tell the nurse
that I have to pack up.
Mona, what texts
are you talking about?
What texts are you
talking about?
Mona.
Hanna, come on.
We're not done with this.
Okay? Do you hear me?
I'm coming back, Mona.
Sorry to disturb you.
Do you have a minute?
Sure. But if
this is about Aria--
It's Emily.
What about her?
Well, I saw her after
the makeup exam yesterday,
and she was...distraught.
She thought she did poorly.
I don't know
if Aria's motioned it,
but I've been helping her
prep for these exams, and--
What is your question?
I just wanted to know
how she did.
She did...fine.
There's a lot riding
on this for her.
Now, maybe if she could
take it again--
There's no need for her
to take it again, Ezra.
I understand
what she's gone through.
Emily did very well.
We're all rooting
for her to succeed.
Great.
That's all she said?
Isn't that enough?
No. That is not enough.
You have to go back
to Radley, Han. Alone.
It's not so easy. Caleb is all over me.
I don't need to know that.
Well, Caleb's not finding
dug-up jewelry in his locker.
Whose earring did Ali find in my dad's couch?
One question at a time.
You're not gonna ask your mom why
she's suddenly defending Garrett?
I mean, seriously, Spencer,
what is that?
He probably told her
it's time to lock Jenna up.
She was driving that night,
guys. I remembered. Clearly.
We believe you, okay?
But honestly, I don't think that you
remember anything clearly from that night.
When we picked you up
you kept calling me "Arlene."
Guys, she can see. She's
probably on Mona's payroll.
Mona does not have any cash. They
won't even let her have floss.
Okay, let's just
do this at lunch.
I can't be late again.
I'll be right back.
I just need to rinse
my water bottle.
Jenna's coming in here.
Where's the earring?
What? Give me the earring.
I have an idea.
What are we doing?
Do I get to slap her again?
No!
Okay, get in the stalls.
Go! Go!
I knew it. That is it. I'm going
for way more than a slap.
Hanna, stop.
Stop why?!
Don't look at me. I'm ready to hang a sign--
"Bitch can see."
She doesn't know that we know.
She will in a minute.
No. We don't let her know
that we know. Not yet.
We can use this...
And we will.
This is all we got.
Season hasn't
really started yet.
We usually don't get
our shipment till next month.
You want all these hoodies too?
You got it.
So...
You buy all these for a team?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com